NexusFont 2.6.2 (2.6.2.1870) - 2015.11.06

- Added: default_light skin added (edit nexusfont.ini file to change skin)
- Color scheme for left library panel is now editable (edit skin.xml file)
- Fixed: font file has style(bold, italic) display error when anti-alias is on 
- Fixed: deleting load failed fonts didn't work
- Croatian language added

NexusFont 2.6.1 (2.6.1.1853) - 2015.10.25

- Fixed: font file has style(bold, italic) display error 
- Fixed: hang when loading broken fonts
- Japanese and Swedish language update

NexusFont 2.6.0 (2.6.0.1820) - 2015.10.11

- New Look! Great looking on Windows 10.
- Tag AND/OR search mode option added.
- Bug fixes

NexusFont 2.5.8 (2.5.8.1582) - 2012.7.5

- Fixed: Help menu link error
- Fixed: The number of fonts in a set displayed as 0
- Fixed: Some open type fonts were not printed properly

NexusFont 2.5.7 (2.5.7.1562) - 2011.12.28

- Improved: Sorting Library/Sets sub-items
- Changed: Main icon design
- Added: Delete function on failed to load window.
- Improved: Font files can be dragged from Explorer to a font set
- Fixed: Font > Open folder didn't work
- Fixed: Bugs related with tags are fixed

NexusFont 2.5.6 (2.5.6.1478) - 2011.07.03

- Added: Edit > Select Same Family (Ctrl + Y) function added
- Improved: Tags can be added or replaced
- Fixed: Cannot use Ctrl+A shortcut in sample text edit box
- Fixed: Error occurred when opening a properties dialog on Type1 font
- Fixed: Some CJK fonts are not displayed correctly
- Fixed: Some Open Type fonts are not displayed correctly
- Fixed: Type1 font rename error

NexusFont 2.5.5 (2.5.5.1420) - 2010.09.23

- Fixed: cannot delete library group
- Fixed: Dialogs are broken on some Windows
- Fixed: Move to/Copy to submenu only shows number

NexusFont 2.5.4 (2.5.4.1400) - 2010.08.16

- Added: Drag & Drop from font list to library panel or trash button
- Added: Font information panel
- Added: Sort by vendor
- Improved: Smooth Scroll
- Improved: UpdateCheck.exe removed. Now update check is done internally.
- Fixed: Some characters was cropped in Character Map dialog large view.

NexusFont 2.5.3 (2.5.3.1142) - 2010.05.31

- Added: Include fonts in subfolders (View > Include Subfolders)
- Fixed: Settings are changed after restoring from minimized window with 'hide when minized'.
- Several bugs are fixed

NexusFont 2.5 (2.5.2.1120) - 2010.05.16

- Added: Adding font folder to a group by Drag&Drop from Explorer
- Improved: Font folder tooltip displaying folder full path on Library Pane
- Several bugs are fixed

NexusFont 2.5 beta (2.5.1.1110) - 2010.05.12

- Improved: Windows 7 compatibility
- Improved: Redesign Main UI
- Added: You can put tags on fonts and search with tags
- Improved: Manages font folders by group
- Added: Hide when minimized option added
- Added: Show font name in english option added
- Improved: Portable - can be run in USB memory with font files in it
- Added: shift + click selection
- Added: Install/Uninstall Log: You can see install/unistall log by selecting [Help > Install/Uninstall Log] menu
- Fixed: QuickSearch problem when searching in CJK
- Redsign Icon 
- Some minor bugs are fixed



NexusFont 2 (2.0.1.1075) - 2008.07.07

- Improved: Charmap window can be resized.
- Fixed: "Invalid Date" error message is shown while loading fonts
- Some minor bugs are fixed



NexusFont 2 RC3 - 2008.05.13
 
- Improved: speed up find duplicate fonts function.
- Fixed: finding duplicate fonts stopped when there is an invalid font.
- Added: select All, Deselect All buttons are added on a find duplicate fonts dialog.
- Fixed: selection list is invalid after moving or deleting font files.
- Improved: favorite fonts can be added by dragging and drop directly from Windows Explorer or other file managers.
- Added: Anti-Aliasing option is added on an Export as Image dialog
- Improved: full support for Adobe Type1 font (Copy To/Move To/Rename/Install/Uninstall)
- Added: font information can be shown in various languages on a properties dialog when a font file include those information.
- Improved: font files error occurred while loading will be shown after loading fonts so users can check and delete those invalid fonts.
